<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Welcome to Linutil Docs on Linutil</title>
    <link>http://localhost:1313/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Welcome to Linutil Docs on Linutil</description>
    <generator>Hugo</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <copyright>Copyright (c) 2020-2024 ChrisTitusTech</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 22 Feb 2025 16:04:48 +0200</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="http://localhost:1313/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Example Post</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/blog/example-post/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 07 Sep 2023 16:27:22 +0200</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/blog/example-post/</guid>
      <description>You can use blog posts for announcing product updates and features.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Getting Started</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/docs/start-here/getting-started/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 20 Feb 2025 12:07:48 +0200</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/docs/start-here/getting-started/</guid>
      <description>&lt;br&gt;&#xA;&lt;img src=&#34;http://localhost:1313/images/cttlogo.png&#34; width=&#34;50&#34;&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2 id=&#34;chris-titus-techs-linux-utility&#34;&gt;Chris Titus Tech&amp;rsquo;s Linux Utility&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Linutil&lt;/strong&gt; is a distro-agnostic toolbox designed to simplify everyday Linux tasks. It helps users set up applications and optimize their systems for specific use cases. Developed in &lt;strong&gt;Rust&lt;/strong&gt; 🦀, Linutil delivers exceptional performance and reliability.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Installation</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/docs/start-here/installation/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 20 Feb 2025 20:51:12 +0200</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/docs/start-here/installation/</guid>
      <description>&lt;div class=&#34;callout callout-note d-flex flex-row mt-4 mb-4 pt-4 pe-4 pb-2 ps-3&#34;&gt;&#xD;&#xA;  &lt;svg&#xA;  xmlns=&#34;http://www.w3.org/2000/svg&#34;&#xA;  width=&#34;24&#34;&#xA;  height=&#34;24&#34;&#xA;  viewBox=&#34;0 0 24 24&#34;&#xA;  fill=&#34;none&#34;&#xA;  stroke=&#34;currentColor&#34;&#xA;  stroke-width=&#34;2&#34;&#xA;  stroke-linecap=&#34;round&#34;&#xA;  stroke-linejoin=&#34;round&#34;&#xA; &#xA; class=&#34;outline/info-circle svg-inline callout-icon me-2 mb-3&#34; id=&#34;svg-info-circle&#34; role=&#34;img&#34;&gt;&#xA;  &lt;path stroke=&#34;none&#34; d=&#34;M0 0h24v24H0z&#34; fill=&#34;none&#34;/&gt;&#xA;  &lt;path d=&#34;M3 12a9 9 0 1 0 18 0a9 9 0 0 0 -18 0&#34; /&gt;&#xA;  &lt;path d=&#34;M12 9h.01&#34; /&gt;&#xA;  &lt;path d=&#34;M11 12h1v4h1&#34; /&gt;&#xA;&lt;/svg&gt;&#xD;&#xA;  &lt;div class=&#34;callout-content&#34;&gt;&#xD;&#xA;    &#xD;&#xA;    &lt;div class=&#34;callout-body&#34;&gt;&#xD;&#xA;      &lt;p&gt;NOTE:&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Code of Conduct</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/docs/meta/code-of-conduct/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 22 Feb 2025 16:04:48 +0200</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/docs/meta/code-of-conduct/</guid>
      <description>&lt;img src=&#34;http://localhost:1313/images/code-of-conduct.png&#34; width=&#34;50&#34;&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2 id=&#34;our-pledge&#34;&gt;Our Pledge&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;We as members, contributors, and leaders pledge to make participation in our&#xA;community a harassment-free experience for everyone, regardless of age, body&#xA;size, visible or invisible disability, ethnicity, sex characteristics, gender&#xA;identity and expression, level of experience, education, socio-economic status,&#xA;nationality, personal appearance, race, religion, or sexual identity&#xA;and orientation.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Contributing</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/docs/meta/contributing/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 22 Feb 2025 16:04:48 +0200</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/docs/meta/contributing/</guid>
      <description>&lt;img src=&#34;http://localhost:1313/images/contribute.png&#34; width=&#34;50&#34;&gt;&#xA;&lt;br&gt; &#xA;&lt;p&gt;Thank you for considering contributing to Linutil! We appreciate your effort in helping improve this project. To ensure that your contributions align with the goals and quality standards of Linutil, please follow these guidelines:&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Roadmap</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/docs/meta/roadmap/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 22 Feb 2025 16:04:48 +0200</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/docs/meta/roadmap/</guid>
      <description>&lt;img src=&#34;http://localhost:1313/images/roadmap.png&#34; width=&#34;50&#34;&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2 id=&#34;vision&#34;&gt;Vision&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;To simplify linux tasks for all users for all distributions; Easily, efficiently, and effortlessly.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2 id=&#34;goals&#34;&gt;Goals&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;input disabled=&#34;&#34; type=&#34;checkbox&#34;&gt; Focus on tasks that take time in Linux and automate them. (Example: Removing a user, adding a user, etc. - but mostly BASH scripts with POSIX compliance.)&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;input checked=&#34;&#34; disabled=&#34;&#34; type=&#34;checkbox&#34;&gt; Remove Binary linutil from being tracked in git and make it a github action.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;input disabled=&#34;&#34; type=&#34;checkbox&#34;&gt; Document every function and feature of linutil. (Preview panel description addition)&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;input checked=&#34;&#34; disabled=&#34;&#34; type=&#34;checkbox&#34;&gt; Create a discord server for linutil and invite the community.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;input checked=&#34;&#34; disabled=&#34;&#34; type=&#34;checkbox&#34;&gt; Power Optimizations for Laptops&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2 id=&#34;milestones&#34;&gt;Milestones&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;h3 id=&#34;q4-2024&#34;&gt;Q4 2024&lt;/h3&gt;&#xA;&lt;ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;input checked=&#34;&#34; disabled=&#34;&#34; type=&#34;checkbox&#34;&gt; Finish the foundation of the project&amp;rsquo;s CLI&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;input checked=&#34;&#34; disabled=&#34;&#34; type=&#34;checkbox&#34;&gt; Implement CLI arguments and configuration support&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;input checked=&#34;&#34; disabled=&#34;&#34; type=&#34;checkbox&#34;&gt; Add an option for logging script executions&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;h3 id=&#34;q1-2025&#34;&gt;Q1 2025&lt;/h3&gt;&#xA;&lt;ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;input disabled=&#34;&#34; type=&#34;checkbox&#34;&gt; GUI Brainstorming and Planning&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;input disabled=&#34;&#34; type=&#34;checkbox&#34;&gt; Basic GUI Implementation&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;h3 id=&#34;q2-2025&#34;&gt;Q2 2025&lt;/h3&gt;&#xA;&lt;ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;input disabled=&#34;&#34; type=&#34;checkbox&#34;&gt; Full GUI Implementation&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2 id=&#34;community-feedback&#34;&gt;Community Feedback&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Encourage community input and suggestions for future development.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>User Guide</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/docs/guides/user-guide/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 21 Feb 2025 16:04:48 +0200</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/docs/guides/user-guide/</guid>
      <description>&lt;h2 id=&#34;application-setup&#34;&gt;Application Setup&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;h3 id=&#34;communication-apps&#34;&gt;Communication Apps&lt;/h3&gt;&#xA;&lt;ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Discord&lt;/strong&gt;: Discord is a versatile communication platform for gamers and communities, offering voice, video, and text chat features.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Jitsi&lt;/strong&gt;: Jitsi Meet is an open-source video conferencing tool that allows users to host and join secure meetings directly from their web browsers without the need for downloads.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Signal&lt;/strong&gt;: Signal is a privacy-focused messaging app that provides end-to-end encryption for secure text, voice, and video communication.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Slack&lt;/strong&gt;: Slack is a collaboration platform designed for team communication, featuring channels, direct messaging, file sharing, and integrations with various productivity tools.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Telegram&lt;/strong&gt;: Telegram is a cloud-based messaging app known for its speed and security, offering features like group chats, channels, and end-to-end encrypted calls.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Thunderbird&lt;/strong&gt;: Thunderbird is a free, open-source email client that offers powerful features like customizable email management, a built-in calendar, and extensive add-ons for enhanced functionality.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Zoom&lt;/strong&gt;: Zoom is a widely-used video conferencing platform that allows users to host virtual meetings, webinars, and online collaboration with features like screen sharing and recording.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;h3 id=&#34;developer-tools&#34;&gt;Developer Tools&lt;/h3&gt;&#xA;&lt;ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Github Desktop&lt;/strong&gt;: GitHub Desktop is a user-friendly application that simplifies the process of managing Git repositories and interacting with GitHub, providing a graphical interface for tasks like committing, branching, and syncing changes.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;JetBrains Toolbox&lt;/strong&gt;: JetBrains Toolbox is a collection of tools and an app that help developers work with JetBrains products.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Meld&lt;/strong&gt;: Meld is a visual diff and merge tool that helps compare files, directories, and version-controlled projects.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Neovim&lt;/strong&gt;: Neovim is a refactor, and sometimes redactor, in the tradition of Vim.&#xA;It is not a rewrite but a continuation and extension of Vim.&#xA;This command configures neovim from CTT&amp;rsquo;s neovim configuration.&#xA;https://github.com/ChrisTitusTech/neovim&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Ngrok&lt;/strong&gt;: Ngrok is a tool that creates secure, temporary tunnels to expose local servers to the internet for testing and development.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Sublime Text&lt;/strong&gt;: Sublime Text is a fast, lightweight, and customizable text editor known for its simplicity, powerful features, and wide range of plugins for various programming languages.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;VS Code&lt;/strong&gt;: Visual Studio Code (VS Code) is a lightweight, open-source code editor with built-in support for debugging, version control, and extensions for various programming languages and frameworks.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;VS Codium&lt;/strong&gt;: VSCodium is a free, open-source version of Visual Studio Code (VS Code) that removes Microsoft-specific telemetry and branding.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;h3 id=&#34;web-browsers&#34;&gt;Web Browsers&lt;/h3&gt;&#xA;&lt;ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Brave&lt;/strong&gt;: Brave is a free and open-source web browser developed by Brave Software, Inc. based on the Chromium web browser.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Chromium&lt;/strong&gt;: Chromium is an open-source web browser project started by Google, to provide the source code for the proprietary Google Chrome browser.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Google Chrome&lt;/strong&gt;: Google Chrome is a fast, secure, and free web browser, built for the modern web.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;LibreWolf&lt;/strong&gt;: LibreWolf is a fork of Firefox, focused on privacy, security, and freedom.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Lynx&lt;/strong&gt;: Lynx is a highly configurable text-based web browser for use on cursor-addressable character cell terminals.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Mozilla Firefox&lt;/strong&gt;: Mozilla Firefox is a free and open-source web browser developed by the Mozilla Foundation.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Thorium&lt;/strong&gt;: Thorium is a Chromium-based browser focused on privacy and performance.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Vivaldi&lt;/strong&gt;: Vivaldi is a freeware, cross-platform web browser developed by Vivaldi Technologies.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Tor Browser&lt;/strong&gt;: Tor Browser is a free and open-source firefox-based web browser designed for anonymity and censorship circumvention.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;waterfox&lt;/strong&gt;: Waterfox is the privacy-focused web browser engineered to give you speed, control, and peace of mind on the internet.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Alacritty&lt;/strong&gt;: Alacritty is a modern terminal emulator that comes with sensible defaults, but allows for extensive configuration. By integrating with other applications, rather than reimplementing their functionality, it manages to provide a flexible set of features with high performance. The supported platforms currently consist of BSD, Linux, macOS and Windows. This command installs and configures alacritty terminal emulator.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Android Debloater&lt;/strong&gt;: Universal Android Debloater (UAD) is a tool designed to help users remove bloatware and unnecessary pre-installed applications from Android devices, enhancing performance and user experience.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Bash Prompt&lt;/strong&gt;: The .bashrc file is a script that runs every time a new terminal session is started in Unix-like operating systems. It is used to configure the shell session, set up aliases, define functions, and more, making the terminal easier to use and more powerful. This command configures the key sections and functionalities defined in the .bashrc file from CTT&amp;rsquo;s mybash repository. https://github.com/ChrisTitusTech/mybash&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Bottles&lt;/strong&gt;: Bottles allows Windows software, like applications and games, to run on Linux. Bottles also provides tools to categorize, organize and optimize your applications.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Docker&lt;/strong&gt;: Docker is an open platform that uses OS-level virtualization to deliver software in packages called containers.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Podman&lt;/strong&gt;: Podman is a daemon-less open platform that uses OS-level virtualization to deliver software in packages called containers.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Podman-compose&lt;/strong&gt;: Podman Compose is a tool for defining and running multi-container applications using Podman.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;DWM-Titus&lt;/strong&gt;: DWM is a dynamic window manager for X.&#xA;It manages windows in tiled, monocle and floating layouts.&#xA;All of the layouts can be applied dynamically, optimising the environment for the application in use and the task performed.&#xA;This command installs and configures DWM and a desktop manager.&#xA;The list of patches applied can be found in CTT&amp;rsquo;s DWM repository&#xA;https://github.com/ChrisTitusTech/dwm-titus&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Fastfetch&lt;/strong&gt;: Fastfetch is a neofetch-like tool for fetching system information and displaying it prettily. It is written mainly in C, with performance and customizability in mind. This command installs fastfetch and configures from CTT&amp;rsquo;s mybash repository. https://github.com/ChrisTitusTech/mybash&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Flatpak / Flathub&lt;/strong&gt;: Flatpak is a universal application sandbox for Linux that uses isolated packages from Flathub to prevent conflicts and system alterations, while alleviating dependency concerns. This command installs Flatpak and adds the Flathub repository&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Grub Theme&lt;/strong&gt;: Installs ChrisTitusTech&amp;rsquo;s Top 5 Bootloader Themes script to allow for easy customization of GRUB.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Kitty&lt;/strong&gt;: kitty is a free and open-source GPU-accelerated terminal emulator for Linux, macOS, and some BSD distributions, focused on performance and features. kitty is written in a mix of C and Python programming languages. This command installs and configures kitty.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Linutil Installer&lt;/strong&gt;: Installs a distro-specific Linutil package locally.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Linutil Updater&lt;/strong&gt;: Updates your local Linutil crate installation.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Rofi&lt;/strong&gt;: Rofi is a window switcher, run dialog, ssh-launcher and dmenu replacement that started as a clone of simpleswitcher, written by Sean Pringle and later expanded by Dave Davenport. This command installs and configures rofi with configuration from CTT&amp;rsquo;s DWM repo. https://github.com/ChrisTitusTech/dwm-titus&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Waydroid&lt;/strong&gt;: Waydroid is an emulator that allows you to run Android apps and games on Linux.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;ZSH Prompt&lt;/strong&gt;: The Z shell is a Unix shell that can be used as an interactive login shell and as a command interpreter for shell scripting. Zsh is an extended Bourne shell with many improvements, including some features of Bash, ksh, and tcsh. This command installs ZSH prompt and provides basic configuration.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2 id=&#34;gaming&#34;&gt;Gaming&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;h3 id=&#34;diablo-ii-resurrected&#34;&gt;Diablo II Resurrected&lt;/h3&gt;&#xA;&lt;ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Loot Filter&lt;/strong&gt;: This is a loot filter for Diablo II Resurrected. It&amp;rsquo;s designed to be a simple, clean, and easy to read loot filter that highlights the most important items. Works on battle.net and single player. No frills, no config, just highlights high runes and other valuable items. For more information visit: &lt;a href=&#34;https://github.com/ChrisTitusTech/d2r-loot-filter&#34;&gt;dr2-loot-filter&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2 id=&#34;security&#34;&gt;Security&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Firewall Baselines (CTT)&lt;/strong&gt;: Developed to ease iptables firewall configuration, UFW provides a user friendly way to create an IPv4 or IPv6 host-based firewall. This command installs UFW and configures UFW based on CTT&amp;rsquo;s recommended rules. For more information visit: https://christitus.com/linux-security-mistakes&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2 id=&#34;system-setup&#34;&gt;System Setup&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;Linutil provides streamlined system setup options for &lt;strong&gt;Arch Linux&lt;/strong&gt; and &lt;strong&gt;Fedora&lt;/strong&gt;. Below are the features and tools available:&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Commands</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/docs/start-here/commands/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 20 Feb 2025 16:04:48 +0200</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/docs/start-here/commands/</guid>
      <description>&lt;img src=&#34;http://localhost:1313/images/script.png&#34; width=&#34;50&#34;&gt;&#xD;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;Linutil supports various command-line arguments to customize its behavior. Here are some common arguments you can use:&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;code&gt;-c, --config &amp;lt;CONFIG&amp;gt;&lt;/code&gt; : Path to the configuration file.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;code&gt;--override-validation&lt;/code&gt; : Show all available options, disregarding compatibility checks (UNSAFE).&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;code&gt;--size-bypass&lt;/code&gt; : Bypass the terminal size limit.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;code&gt;-y, --skip-confirmation&lt;/code&gt; : Skip confirmation prompt before executing commands.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;code&gt;-t, --theme &amp;lt;THEME&amp;gt;&lt;/code&gt; : Set the theme to use in the application [default: &lt;code&gt;default&lt;/code&gt;] [possible values: &lt;code&gt;default&lt;/code&gt;, &lt;code&gt;compatible&lt;/code&gt;].&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;code&gt;-h, --help&lt;/code&gt; : Print help.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;For more detailed usage, run:&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
